A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Press Office, Series 25 FA368
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Public Relations File, 1; 59 Cubic Feet
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 714)
  - November 24, 1969 - January 7, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 715)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 716)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 717)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 718)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 719)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 720)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 721)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 722)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 723)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 724)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 725)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 726)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 727)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 728)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 729)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 730)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 731)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 732)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 733)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 734)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 735)
  - January 7, 1970 - January 20, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 736)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 737)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 738)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 739)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 740)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 741)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 742)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 743)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 744)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 745)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 746)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 747)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 748)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 749)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 750)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 751)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 752)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 753)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 754)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 755)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 756)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 757)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 758)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 759)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 760)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 761)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 762)
  - January 21, 1970 - February 23, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 763)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 764)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 765)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 766)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 767)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 768)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 769)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 770)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 771)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 772)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 773)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 774)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 775)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 776)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 777)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 778)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 779)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 780)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 781)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 782)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 783)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 784)
  - February 24, 1970 - April 8, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 785)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 786)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 787)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 788)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 789)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 790)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 791)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 792)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 793)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 794)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 795)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 796)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 797)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 798)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 799)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 800)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 801)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 802)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 803)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 804)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 805)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 806)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 807)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 808)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 809)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 810)
  - April 8, 1970 - May 14, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 811)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 812)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 813)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 814)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 815)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 816)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 817)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 818)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 819)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 820)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 821)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 822)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 823)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 824)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 825)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 826)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 827)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 828)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 829)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 830)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 831)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 832)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 833)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 834)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 835)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 836)
  - May 14, 1970 - June 18, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 837)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 838)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 839)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 840)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 841)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 842)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 843)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 844)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 845)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 846)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 847)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 848)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 849)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 850)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 851)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 852)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 853)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 854)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 855)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 856)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 857)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 858)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 859)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 860)
  - June 18, 1970 - July 25, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 861)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 862)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 863)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 864)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 865)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 866)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 867)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 868)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 869)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 870)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 871)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 872)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 873)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 874)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 875)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 876)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 877)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 878)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 879)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 880)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 881)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 882)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 883)
  - July 27, 1970 - August 19, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 884)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 885)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 886)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 887)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 888)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 889)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 890)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 891)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 892)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 893)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 894)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 895)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 896)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 897)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 898)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 899)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 900)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 901)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 902)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 903)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 904)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 905)
  - August 20, 1970 - September 15, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 906)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 907)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 908)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 909)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 910)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 911)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 912)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 913)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 914)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 915)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 916)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 917)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 918)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 919)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 920)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 921)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 922)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 923)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 924)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 925)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 926)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 927)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 928)
  - September 16, 1970 - October 6, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 929)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 930)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 931)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 932)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 933)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 934)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 935)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 936)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 937)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 938)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 939)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 940)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 941)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 942)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 943)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 944)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 945)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 946)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 947)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 948)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 949)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 950)
  - October 6, 1970 - October 21, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 951)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 952)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 953)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 954)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 955)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 956)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 957)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 958)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 959)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 960)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 961)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 962)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 963)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 964)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 965)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 966)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 967)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 968)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 969)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 970)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 971)
  - October 22, 1970 - November 23, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 972)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 973)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 974)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 975)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 976)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 977)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 978)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 979)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 980)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 981)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 982)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 983)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 984)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 985)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 986)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 987)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 988)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 989)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 990)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 991)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 992)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 993)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 994)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 995)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 996)
  - November 24, 1970 - January 29, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 997)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 998)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 999)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1000)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1001)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1002)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1003)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1004)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1005)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1006)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1007)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1008)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1009)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1010)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1011)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1012)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1013)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1014)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1015)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1016)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1017)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1018)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1019)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1020)
  - January 30, 1971 - March 25, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1021)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1022)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1023)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1024)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1025)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1026)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1027)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1028)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1029)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1030)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1031)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1032)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1033)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1034)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1035)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1036)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1037)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1038)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1039)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1040)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1041)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1042)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1043)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1044)
  - March 26, 1971 - June 14, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1045)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1046)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1047)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1048)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1049)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1050)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1051)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1052)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1053)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1054)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1055)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1056)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1057)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1058)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1059)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1060)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1061)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1062)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1063)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1064)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1065)
  - June 15, 1971 - September 15, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 1066)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1067)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1068)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1069)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1070)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1071)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1072)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1073)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1074)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1075)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1076)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1077)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1078)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1079)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1080)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1081)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1082)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1083)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1084)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1085)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1086)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1087)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1088)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1089)
  - September 16, 1971 - December 3, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 1090)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1091)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1092)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1093)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1094)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1095)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1096)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1097)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1098)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1099)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1100)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1101)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1102)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1103)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1104)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1105)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1106)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1107)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1108)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1109)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1110)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1111)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1112)
  - December 4, 1971 - March 9, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 1113)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 20, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 1114)